Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Shocky Shay - No joke, 1989; SR-30103; Shocky Shay (Box 430)
          Orpheus Records
        - Shoestring - Representin' till the world ends (disc one), 1999; SR-30104; Shoestring (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30105. Double album.
          Catalog # TBCD 1331; A-side Matrix # TB-1331-A MASTERDISK
        - Shoestring - Representin' till the world ends (disc two), 1999; SR-30105; Shoestring (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30104. Double album.
          Catalog # TBCD 1331; A-side Matrix # TB-1331-C MASTERDISK
        - Hi-Tech, Jedi, and Spectrum - Padlock; S.O.S., 1997; SR-30106; Hi-Tech; Jedi; Spectrum; Matrix (Pyramindz) (Box 430)
          Catalog # MV-102; A-side Matrix # MV-102-A
          Mass Vinyl Recordings
        - Shonte' - I'll be your beasty, 1984; SR-30107; Shonte' (Box 430)
          Catalog # SH-32023; A-side Matrix # VID-282-A G TRUTONE-Pa-2-8-4
        - Shootyz Groove - L train, 1999; SR-30108; Shootyz Groove (Box 430)
          Catalog # PRO-A-9832; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9832-A-SR1
          Kinetic Records
        - Short Fat Sally - Sally's attack; Your a pest, 1985; SR-30109; Short Fat Sally; Mac Fresh (Box 430)
          Catalog # SR-903; A-side Matrix # SR-903-Re-1 A VIRTUE 1
          Slice Records
          Westville, New Jersey
        - Shortee - The dreamer, 1999; SR-30110; Shortee (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30111. Double album.
          Catalog # BOMB2042; A-side Matrix # BOMB 2042 A
          Bomb Hip-Hop Records
        - Shortee - The dreamer, 1999; SR-30111; Shortee (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30110. Double album.
          Catalog # BOMB2042; A-side Matrix # BOMB 2042 C
        - G-Shorties (Gangsta Shorties) - Now who could it be, SR-30112; G-Shorties; Gangsta Shorties (Box 430)
          Catalog # SR 1007; A-side Matrix # SR-1007-A FULLERSOUND MF
          Stress Records
          Berkshire, United Kingdom
        - Shotgun - Shake & pop, 1982; SR-30113; Shotgun (Box 430)
          Catalog # 79900; A-side Matrix # 79900-A G-1 2021C MASTERED BY CAPITOL
          Montage Records
        - Showbiz & A.G. - Soul clap; Party groove, SR-30114; Showbiz & A.G. (Box 430)
          Catalog # PAYD 9004-1; A-side Matrix # PAYD-9004-1-A EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 35593 C
          Payday
        - Showbiz & A.G. - Runaway slave, 1992; SR-30115; Showbiz & A.G.; Diamond D; Dres; Big L; Deshawn; Lord Finesse (Box 430)
          Catalog # 828 334-1; A-side Matrix # 422-828-334-1-AS-REV DMM SP 1-1 MASTERDISK TD
        - Shriekback - Sexthinkone, 1982; SR-30116; Shriekback (Box 430)
          Catalog # Y USA 3; A-side Matrix # A-1 12"-Y-USA-3-A
          Y America
        - Shriekback - Nemesis, 1985; SR-30117; Shriekback (Box 430)
          Catalog # 0-96874; A-side Matrix # ST DM-4 8020-1 11 STERLIING
        - Shug & Dap - Anotha man, 1994; SR-30118; Shug & Dap (Box 430)
          Catalog # 0-41681; A-side Matrix # 0-41681-A-SR1-DMM SP 1-1 RB Precision
        - Shug & Dap - Anotha man, 1994; SR-30119; Shug & Dap (Box 430)
        - Shuga Shame - Native New Yorker, 1999; SR-30120; Shuga Shame; Day, Inaya (Box 430)
          Catalog # BPC1999; A-side Matrix # BPC-1999-A
          Bronx Paradise Connections, Inc.
        - Shuga Shame - Native New Yorker, 1999; SR-30121; Shuga Shame; Day, Inaya (Box 430)
        - Shurik'n - J'lève mon verre; Tant de raisons, 1999; SR-30122; Shurik'n; Janik (Box 430)
          Catalog # 7243 89601664; A-side Matrix # 7243 89601664 A ZZED TR DFI- 99 1 1
          Delabel
        - Shy FX - Ebony dubs 5, 2004; SR-13976; Shy FX; T-Power; Love Byte (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-13977. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EBR033; A-side Matrix # EBR-033-A-1 BEAU
          Ebony Recordings
          Leicestershire, United Kingdom
        - Shy FX - Ebony dubs 5, 2004; SR-13977; Shy FX; T-Power; Love Byte (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-13976. 2 copies.
        - Shyheim - 21st century crisis; There she goes, 2004; SR-30123; Shyheim (Box 430)
          Catalog # NE 20541; A-side Matrix # NRVI-20541 A
          Nervous Recordings
        - Shyheim - 21st century crisis; There she goes, 2004; SR-30124; Shyheim (Box 430)
        - Shyheim - Club wax, 1996; SR-30125; Shyheim; Pop "The Brown Hornet"; Squig; Williams, Keemeelah; Grinstead, Lamisha; Down Low Recka; June Luva; Rubbabandz; D.V. Alias Khrist; Smoothe Da Hustler; Trigger Tha Gambler (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30126. Different discs.
          Catalog # 7243 8 41583 1 6; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11093-A MASTERDISK TD
        - Shyheim - This iz real, 1996; SR-30126; Shyheim (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30125. Different discs.
          Catalog # 7243 8 38536 1 8; A-side Matrix # Y-38636-A MASTERDISK TD
        - Shyne - Jimmy Choo, 2004; SR-30127; Shyne; Ashanti (Box 430)
          Catalog # DEFR 16148-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16148-1 A1B RW HFM J.Y.
          Gangland Record Corp.
        - Shyne - Godfather, 2004; SR-30128; Shyne (Box 430)
          Catalog # DEFR 16147-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16147-1 A
        - Shyne - Godfather buried alive (disc one), 2004; SR-30129; Shyne; Brown, Foxy; Kurupt; Nate Dogg; Ashanti (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30130. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002962-01; A-side Matrix # B0002962-01 LP01 A Ricardo-Hit Factory
        - Shyne - Godfather buried alive (disc two), 2004; SR-30130; Shyne; Brown, Foxy; Kurupt; Nate Dogg; Ashanti (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30129. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002962-01; A-side Matrix # B0002962-01 LP02 A
        - Shyne - Godfather buried alive (disc one), 2004; SR-30131; Shyne; Brown, Foxy; Kurupt; Nate Dogg; Ashanti (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30132. Double album.
        - Shyne - Godfather buried alive (disc two), 2004; SR-30132; Shyne; Brown, Foxy; Kurupt; Nate Dogg; Ashanti (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30131. Double album.
        - Shyne - More or less, 2004; SR-30133; Shyne (Box 430)
          Catalog # DEFR 16110-1; A-side Matrix # B0002869·11A X HT-IVI J·Y.
        - Shyne - More or less, 2004; SR-30134; Shyne (Box 431)
        - Shyne - Bambaata 2012 episode 2, 1998; SR-30135; Shyne; Mask; Roni Size (Box 431)
          Catalog # EBR 020TR; A-side Matrix # EBR-020R-A1
        - Shy FX - Bambaata, 1998; SR-30136; Shy FX (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30137. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EBR 015; A-side Matrix # EBR-15-AA- SIMON THE EXCHANGE
        - Shy FX - Bambaata, 1998; SR-30137; Shy FX (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30136. 2 copies.
        - Siamese - Tha bomb, 1998; SR-30138; Siamese (Box 431)
          Catalog # EAS 41285; A-side Matrix # XSS-41285A-1D
        - Sibbles, Leroy - Rock steady party; Rock steady dubbin', 1982; SR-30139; Sibbles, Leroy; Nicodemus (Box 431)
          Catalog # MICCAN 0044; A-side Matrix # MICCAN 0044-A TLC-T
          Micron Music Canada
          Kingston, Ontario, Canada
        - Sid & B-Tonn - Deathwish, 1990; SR-30140; Sid & B-Tonn (Box 431)
          Catalog # 44 73466; A-side Matrix # XSS-73466B- -2A G1 (T) A5 MASTERDISK
        - Side Effect - I can't play; Do it, 1981; SR-30141; Side Effect (Box 431)
          Catalog # AS-11511; A-side Matrix # AS-11511-A 1-1 SP MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
        - Side Effect - Keep on keepin' on, 1978; SR-30142; Side Effect (Box 431)
          Catalog # D-106; A-side Matrix # D 106 A 1-1 KENDUN-C
          Berkeley, California
        - Side Effect - Make you mine, 1981; SR-30143; Side Effect (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30144. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AS-11485; A-side Matrix # AM-11485-A1 SP 1-1 MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
        - Side Effect - Make you mine, 1981; SR-30144; Side Effect (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30143. 2 copies.
        - Sidney - Hip hop, 1984; SR-30145; Sidney (Box 431)
          Catalog # CBS A12.4293; A-side Matrix # E4 3 12 42 93 A 12-293 A T
          Neuilly-sur-Seine, France
        - Sidney - Hip hop, 1984; SR-30146; Sidney (Box 431)
        - Sidney - Hip hop, 1984; SR-30147; Sidney (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30148. 2 copies.
        - Sidney - Hip hop, 1984; SR-30148; Sidney (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30147. 2 copies.
        - Sidney - Let's break, 1984; SR-30149; Sidney; Black White and Co. (Box 431)
          Catalog # 8346; A-side Matrix # 346 A
          Carrere
        - Sidney - Let's break, 1984; SR-30150; Sidney; Black White and Co. (Box 431)
        - Sidney - Let's break, 1984; SR-30151; Sidney; Black White and Co. (Box 431)
          Catalog # 4Z9 05071; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-05071-3-AB P
        - Sidran, Ben - The cat and the hat, 1979; SR-30152; Sidran, Ben (Box 431)
          Catalog # SP-741; A-side Matrix # T1 SP741-AT 1-1 3
        - Siegel, Dan - Dan Siegel, 1982; SR-30153; Siegel, Dan (Box 431)
          Catalog # E1-60037; A-side Matrix # E1-60037-A5-SP 1-1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Change, 2005; SR-30154; Sigel, Beanie (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 16345-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16345-1A MASTEREDISK TD
          Damon Dash Music Group
        - Sigel, Beanie - The B.coming (disc one), 2005; SR-30155; Sigel, Beanie; Melissa Jay; Freeway; Young Chris; Redman; Peedi Peedi; Twista; Snoop Dogg; Bun B; Rell (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30156. Double album.
          Catalog # B0003082-01; A-side Matrix # B0003082-01-LP01-A-RE1
        - Sigel, Beanie - The B.coming (disc two), 2005; SR-30156; Sigel, Beanie; Grand Puba; Sadat X; Oschino; Sparks; Jay-Z; Cam'ron (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30155. Double album.
          Catalog # B0003082-01; A-side Matrix # B0003082-01-LP02-C-RE1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Roc the mic, 2001; SR-30157; Sigel, Beanie; Freeway (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 15476-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 15476-1 A X1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Think it's a game, 2001; SR-30158; Sigel, Beanie; Freeway; Jay-Z; Young Chris; Daz (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 15407-1; A-side Matrix # 314588 766-1 A X1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Gotta have it, 2004; SR-30159; Sigel, Beanie; Peedi Crakk; Twista (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 16151-1; A-side Matrix # B00035341-1-A1 1 MASTERDISK TD
        - Sigel, Beanie - The reason (disc one), 2001; SR-30160; Sigel, Beanie; Memphis Bleek; Daz (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30161. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15354-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15354-1-A 1 MASTERDISK TD
        - Sigel, Beanie - The reason (disc two), 2001; SR-30161; Sigel, Beanie; Freeway; Jay-Z; Young Chris; Kurupt; Sparks; Scarface; Rell (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30160. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15355-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15355-1-A 1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Feel it in the air, 2005; SR-30162; Sigel, Beanie; Melissa Jay (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 16229-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR -16229-1 A X1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Wanted (On the run), 2004; SR-30163; Sigel, Beanie; Cam'ron (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 16101-1; A-side Matrix # B0002909-11 A TRYTONE NYC Can1 5-04
        - Sigel, Beanie - The B.coming (disc one), 2005; SR-30164; Sigel, Beanie; Melissa Jay; Freeway; Young Chris; Redman; Peedi Peedi; Twista; Snoop Dogg; Bun B; Rell (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30165. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16162-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-161641-C1
        - Sigel, Beanie - The B.coming (disc two), 2005; SR-30165; Sigel, Beanie; Grand Puba; Sadat X; Oschino; Sparks; Jay-Z; Cam'ron (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30164. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16162-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-161641-D1
        - Sigel, Beanie - Feel it in the air, 2005; SR-30166; Sigel, Beanie; Melissa Jay (Box 431)
          Catalog # DEFR 16229-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16229-1 A
        - Sight Beyond Light - Have faith; Tables turn, 2002; SR-30167; Sight Beyond Light (Box 431)
          Catalog # DC-113; A-side Matrix # DC-113-A
          Deep Concentration
        - Sights - Virginia, 1983; SR-30168; Sights (Box 431)
          Catalog # GG-81200; A-side Matrix # A+M-GG-081200A-ES1 EMW
          Gold Mountain
        - Sigler, Bunny - By the way you dance (I knew it was you), 1979; SR-30169; Sigler, Bunny (Box 431)
          Catalog # GG 403 (DJ); A-side Matrix # GG-403-A-10 STERLING
          Gold Mine Records
        - Sign 13 - Degree E.P. Vol. 1, 2004; SR-30170; Sign 13 (Box 431)
          Catalog # DLP-014; A-side Matrix # DLP-014A F/W GV
          Delic Records
          Minamihoncho, Kanto, Japan
        - Sign - Sign of the times, SR-30171; Sign (Box 431)
          Catalog # TREE 005; A-side Matrix # TREE 005 A L-47195 Metropolis Mastering Chicago M.T.C.
          Tree Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Sign - Sign of the times, 1996; SR-30172; Sign (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30211. Different discs.
        - DJ Icey - Treehouse; Picture, 1996; SR-30211; DJ Icey (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30172. Different discs.
          Catalog # TREE 004; A-side Matrix # BRX TREE 004 New S.de L-46659-X M.M.M.J.R.
        - Signal Federation - The naked party's remixes, 1999; SR-30173; Signal Federation; Peace Division; Protein Boy (Box 431)
          Catalog # MA008; A-side Matrix # 08 40570 20 1E1 MA 008 LOUD A
          Mighty Atom Recordings
        - Sigue Sigue Sputnik - Love missile F1-11, 1986; SR-30174; Sigue Sigue Sputnik (Box 431)
          Catalog # V-56021; A-side Matrix # V1-56021 X240915 A Z2 MASTERDISK 1-1
          Manhattan Records
        - Silas, Alfie - You put the L in love, 1983; SR-30175; Silas, Alfie (Box 431)
          Catalog # JD-13605; A-side Matrix # PD-13605-A-1
        - Silent Majority - Curfew (disc one), 1994; SR-30176; Silent Majority (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30177. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # UR 9 DMX; A-side Matrix # UR 9 DMX A1 SNA
        - Silent Majority - Curfew (disc two), 1994; SR-30177; Silent Majority (Box 431)
          In same jacket as # SR-30176. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # UR 9 DMX; A-side Matrix # UR 9 DMX C1 SNA
        - Silk - Midnight dancer, 1979; SR-30178; Silk (Box 431)
          Catalog # 4Z8 3690; A-side Matrix # BA-428-3690-3 STERLING Jr
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Silk, J.M. - Shadows of your love, 1986; SR-30179; Silk, J.M. (Box 431)
          Catalog # DJ 777; A-side Matrix # DJ-777-A RE MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
          D.J. International Records
        - Silkk The Shocker - The shocker, 1996; SR-30180; Silkk The Shocker (Box 431)
          Catalog # SPRO 30078; A-side Matrix # SPRO 30078-A S-33681
          No Limit Records
        - Silkk The Shocker - He did that, 2000; SR-30181; Silkk The Shocker; Master P; Mac (Box 431)
          Catalog # 08724 81421 12; A-side Matrix # 087424-81421-1-A S-44737
        - Silvah Bullet/Silver Bullet - Jewelz and diamondz, 1998; SR-30182; Silvah Bullet; Silver Bullet; Dafunkstarz; Decoder; Deckwrecka (Box 431)
          Catalog # ART015TJX; A-side Matrix # ART015TJX A1 DAMONT
          Arthrob
        - Silvah Bullet/Silver Bullet - Jewelz and diamondz, 1998; SR-30183; Silvah Bullet; Silver Bullet (Box 431)
          Catalog # ART015TJ; A-side Matrix # ART 015 TJ A1
        - Silvah Bullet/Silver Bullet - Dem beas, 1998; SR-30184; Silvah Bullet; Silver Bullet (Box 431)
          Catalog # ART008; A-side Matrix # ART 008 A1 WARD 10 ALPHA DAMONT MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE
        - Silver Convention - Spend the night with me; Mission to Venus, 1978; SR-30185; Silver Convention (Box 431)
          Catalog # MCA-13906; A-side Matrix # MCA 1477 W1
          Midsong International
        - Silver Convention - Get up and boogie; Fly, robin, fly, 1979; SR-30186; Silver Convention (Box 431)
          Catalog # MD 511; A-side Matrix # MD 511A-1A
        - Silver, Karen - Set me free, 1981; SR-30187; Silver, Karen (Box 431)
          Catalog # QRFC 001; A-side Matrix # QRFC 001-A STERLING
          Quality
          Scarborough, Ontario, Canada
        - Silver, Karen - Hold on I'm coming, 1979; SR-30188; Silver, Karen (Box 431)
          Catalog # AB 4248; A-side Matrix # AB-4248-SB-CT2 1T STERLING
        - Silver Star - Eei eei o, 1982; SR-30189; Silver Star (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30190. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # ER-6025; A-side Matrix # EN-1151-1 MASTERDISK-BK
          Enjoy Records
        - Silver Star - Eei eei o, 1982; SR-30190; Silver Star (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30189. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Silver Star - Eei eei o, 1982; SR-30191; Silver Star (Box 432)
        - Simeone, Harry - The little drummer boy: sing we now of Christmas, 1976; SR-30192; Simeone, Harry (Box 432)
          Catalog # FOX 1007; A-side Matrix # J08P-2065-2N B1 R
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Simmons, Aleese - I want it, 1988; SR-30193; Simmons, Aleese (Box 432)
          Catalog # D1-75601; A-side Matrix # D-1-1-75601-2-DMM SP1-3 23127 B-33495-21-DMM SP-AR
        - Simmons, Aleese - I want to be your lover, 1988; SR-30194; Simmons, Aleese (Box 432)
          Catalog # V-72657; A-side Matrix # V-1-72657-21-DMM SP 1-1
        - Simmons, Chandra - Never gonna' let you go, 1987; SR-30195; Simmons, Chandra (Box 432)
          Catalog # FRE-0013; A-side Matrix # FRE-12-X MASTERDISK
          Fresh Records
        - Simmons, Chuck - Hustler's strut, 2003; SR-30196; Simmons, Chuck (Box 432)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0050; A-side Matrix # DEL LP 0050 A
          Funky Delicacies
        - Simmons, Patrick - So wrong, 1983; SR-30197; Simmons, Patrick (Box 432)
          Catalog # 0-67929-A; A-side Matrix # 0-67929-AS-1-SP JS-KENDUN 1-1
        - Simmons, Richard - Reach, 1982; SR-30198; Simmons, Richard (Box 432)
          Catalog # E1-60122-A; A-side Matrix # E1-60122-A-1-RE-SP 1-2 SM2-2 Precision SM
        - Simms, Chavel - Give it up, 1995; SR-30199; Simms, Chavel (Box 432)
          Catalog # CR-352; A-side Matrix # CR-352-3-1-1
        - Simon and Garfunkel - Bridge over troubled water, 1971; SR-30200; Simon and Garfunkel (Box 432)
          Catalog # 1-467256; A-side Matrix # XSLP-219 C 137665 III
          Discos CBS
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Simon and McQueen - I'm down if you're down, 1981; SR-30201; Simon and McQueen (Box 432)
          Catalog # ML9 1001; A-side Matrix # ML9-1001-A 1X 13299 GEL STERLING
          Landmark Records
        - Simon, Carly - Why, 1982; SR-30202; Simon, Carly; Chic (Box 432)
          Catalog # DMD 340; A-side Matrix # ST-DM 41604-1 SP MASTERDISK RL 1-1
        - Simon, Carly - Boys in the trees, 1978; SR-30203; Simon, Carly (Box 432)
          Catalog # 6E-128; A-side Matrix # 6E-128-A-SPIRE-2123
        - Simon, David - Transistor, 1984; SR-30204; Simon, David (Box 432)
          Catalog # 8330; A-side Matrix # 8330 A YD
        - Simon, Joe - Drowning in the sea of love, 1972; SR-30205; Simon, Joe (Box 432)
          Catalog # SEW 021; A-side Matrix # DMD-2694 A-1/2-90 C
          Southbound
        - Simon, Joe - Love vibration, 1978; SR-30206; Simon, Joe (Box 432)
          Catalog # PRO 057; A-side Matrix # PRO-78-NP-3863-GD-2 FW K-10202 GOL
          Spring Records
        - Simon, Lowrell - Love massage, 1981; SR-30207; Simon, Lowrell (Box 432)
          Catalog # 4W9 02617; A-side Matrix # 4W9-02617-1A
          Zoo York Recordz
        - Simon, Paul - Graceland, 1986; SR-30208; Simon, Paul (Box 432)
          Catalog # 1-25447; A-side Matrix # 12 5447-A-RE2-SH1-DMM B-23620-Re2-SH1 STERLING DMM AL-SP 0-6
        - Simon, Paul - The boy in the bubble (Extended version), 1986; SR-30209; Simon, Paul (Box 432)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2652; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2652-SH1 B-26457-SH1 15424 1-1
        - Simone, Nina - In concert - Emergency ward!, 1972; SR-30210; Simone, Nina (Box 432)
          Catalog # LSP-4757; A-side Matrix # BPRS 5349 2S H
        - Simone, Nina - My baby just cares for me, 1997; SR-30212; Simone, Nina (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30213. Different discs.
          Catalog # 20-99001; A-side Matrix # 20-9900-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 64748 DOW GROSSINGER
          Bethlehem Records
        - Supafix - Sound of New Yorkshire EP, 2000; SR-30213; Supafix (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30212. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFR 008; A-side Matrix # EURODISC MPO AFR 008 A1 LOUD
          Afro Art
        - Simone, Nina - Nina Simone at Town Hall, 1959; SR-30214; Simone, Nina (Box 432)
          Catalog # CP-409; A-side Matrix # CP 409 A-2 SR
          Colpix Records
        - Simphonia - You and me, 1986; SR-30215; Simphonia (Box 432)
          Catalog # DMD 927; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49680-49678-3 1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D K
          Cotillion
        - Simplé E - dē abyss, 1994; SR-30216; Simplé E; Spice 1 (Box 432)
          Catalog # FOX DJ-64254; A-side Matrix # SPRO FOX DJ 64254 A
          Fox Records
        - Simple Minds - Promised you a miracle, 1982; SR-30217; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # VS 488-12; A-side Matrix # VS-488-12-A-1 BILBO Tape One
        - Simple Minds - Sister feelings call, 1981; SR-30218; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # 205 154; A-side Matrix # DM 205154 A-2784 S III III
        - Simple Minds - Someone somewhere (in summertime), 1982; SR-30219; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # VS 538-12; A-side Matrix # VS-538-12-A1 0 TOWNHOUSE
        - Simple Minds - Don't you (forget about me), 1985; SR-30220; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # VS 749-12; A-side Matrix # VS 74912 A-1U-1-1-
        - Simple Minds - Don't you (forget about me), 1985; SR-30221; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30222. Different discs.
        - Simple Minds - Don't you (forget about me), 1985; SR-30222; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          In same jacket as # SR-30221. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12125; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO-ES1 SPO-12125-A
          A&M Records
        - Simple Minds - Celebrate, 1980; SR-30223; Simple Minds; Kerr, James (Box 432)
          Catalog # ARIST 12394; A-side Matrix # ARISTA 12394 A//1 ETH TOWNHOUSE
        - Simple Minds - Promised you a miracle, 1982; SR-30224; Simple Minds; Kerr, James (Box 432)
          Catalog # SP-12057; A-side Matrix # AM SPP12057-A ES1 MW3
        - Simple Minds - All the things she said; Don't you (forget about me) live, 1985; SR-30225; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # SP-12177; A-side Matrix # A&M -SP-012177-A-ES1 MASTERDISK
        - Simple Minds - Promised you a miracle; Book of brilliant things; Glittering prize; Celebrate (Simple Minds) live, 1987; SR-30226; Simple Minds (Box 432)
          Catalog # 009446; A-side Matrix # M9 356383 2 9446 A 21
        - Simple Minds - Promised you a miracle, 1982; SR-30227; Simple Minds; Kerr, James (Box 432)
          Catalog # SP-12057; A-side Matrix # AM SPP12057-A ES2 MW3
        - Simple Minds - Don't you (forget about me), 1985; SR-30228; Simple Minds (Box 432)
        - Simple Simon - La bamba, 1994; SR-30229; Simple Simon; Panhead (Box 432)
          Catalog # PRO-7421-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7421-0A AATB
        - Simpleton - Cool yah, 1996; SR-30230; Simpleton; Trowers, Waynie (Box 432)
          Catalog # SMPX-221; A-side Matrix # SPMX 221-A COOL YAH
          Kataliss
        - Simpleton - Coca Cola shape; Pressure, 1992; SR-30231; Simpleton; Brown, Lewin (Box 432)
          Catalog # VPRD-913; A-side Matrix # VPRD 913-A COCOA COLA SHAPE PAUL
        - Simplicious - Let her feel it, 1984; SR-30232; Simplicious (Box 432)
          Catalog # DMD 734; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46341-1 1-1